emptylighthouse.com 2017-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Empty Lighthouse Magazine

We will protect your privacy by not sharing your email address or any other contact information with anyone. By signing up for our magazine, you agree to newsletters from the site, but may opt out at any time.

By submitting information, you agree to Empty Lighthouse Magazine's use of such information for publishing consideration. 

Artwork/Articles published on the site may be removed at anytime by the artist or their representatives, if requested. Such a request will be subject to a formal review.

The public feed is moderated by Empty Lighthouse and our users. 

Any information posted on the public feed is solely the responsibility of the user. When you share information or content like photos, videos, and links via the public feed, you should think carefully about what you are making public.

Empty Lighthouse uses cookies. A cookie is nothing more than a small text file that resides on your hard drive. 

Empty Lighthouse Magazine uses cookies to maintain the login status for those users who have an account with our site. You will not be able to use this feature if your browser client is set to refuse cookies.

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [legal@westbourneinterational.com](mailto:legal@westbourneinterational.com). 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

Empty Lighthouse allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our web site. 

These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. 

These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

For ads served by Google or DoubleClick Ad Exchange (which are not associated with this site), you can see additional information and manage your privacy settings here. 

For ads served by certain other networks, you can learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or opt-out of this type of advertising at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. If you have additional questions or comments, please contact us.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. 

These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may [legal@westbourneinterational.com](mailto:legal@westbourneinterational.com)
